Kheel, Theodore W. Books and Articles 6021/008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Commercial Arbitration Rules, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Commercial Arbitration Rules, 1986; Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Author: American Arbitration Association (AAA)
- The Complexity of Black Progress, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Complexity of Black Progress, 2004; Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Author: Marc H. Morial; Samuel L. Myers, Jr.; Charles J. Ogletree, Jr.; Edmund W. Gordon; David R. Williams; Dennis W. Archer; James R. Lanier; Kenya L. Covington; Melinda F. Emerson; Ronald O. Ross
    Notes: The State of Black America, 2004
- Collective Bargaining: New Dimensions in Labor Relations, 1979; Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining: New Dimensions in Labor Relations, 1979; Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Author: Wayne L. Horvitz; William W. Winpisinger; Theodore W. Kheel; Glenn E. Watts; Benjamin F. Bailar; Albert Shanker; Sol C. Chaikin; Malcolm L. Denise; Ernest G. Green; Jerome M. Rosow; Franklin J. Havelick
    Notes: Edited by Franklin J. Havelick; Foreward and one chapter by Theodore Kheel.
  - Item 2: Collective Bargaining: New Dimensions in Labor Relations, 1979; Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Notes: Edited by Franklin J. Havelick; Foreward and one chapter by Theodore Kheel. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Collective Bargaining: New Dimensions in Labor Relations, 1979; Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Notes: Edited by Franklin J. Havelick; Foreward and one chapter by Theodore Kheel. Copy 3.
- Collective Bargaining and Community Disputes, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining and Community Disputes, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Notes: Reprinted from Monthly Labor Review, January 1969.
  - Item 2: Collective Bargaining and Community Disputes, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Notes: Reprinted from Monthly Labor Review, January 1969. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Collective Bargaining and Community Disputes, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    Notes: Reprinted from Monthly Labor Review, January 1969. Copy 3.
- Collective Bargaining by British Local Authority Employees, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining by British Local Authority Employees, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Author: Harold M. Levinson
  - Item 2: Collective Bargaining by British Local Authority Employees, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
- The Collective Bargaining Forum, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: The Collective Bargaining Forum, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Author: Institute of Collective Bargaining and Group Relations
    Notes: May 12-13, 1969. Information flyer.
  - Item 2: The Collective Bargaining Forum, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: May 12-13, 1969. Information flyer. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: The Collective Bargaining Forum, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: May 12-13, 1969. Information flyer. Copy 23
  - Item 4: The Collective Bargaining Forum, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: May 12-13, 1969. Pre-Forum program.
  - Item 5: The Collective Bargaining Forum, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: May 12-13, 1969. Pre-Forum program. Copy 2.
  - Item 6: The Collective Bargaining Forum, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Notes: May 12-13, 1969. Pre-Forum program. Copy 3.
- Collective Bargaining In Hospitals, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining In Hospitals: A Plan to Resolve Impasses, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Author: Lewis B. Kaden; Theodore W. Kheel
    Notes: Paper delivered at IRRA Conference, December 30, 1969.
- Collective Bargaining in the Basic Steel Industry, 1961; Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining in the Basic Steel Industry: A Study of the Public Interest and the Role of Government, 1961; Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Author: United States Department of Labor
- A Collective Bargaining Institute, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: A Collective Bargaining Institute: Theodore Kheel, Spirit Behind the New Venture, Speaks Out on the Reason and the Need, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Author: American Labor
    Notes: Published in American Labor, v.1:no.3 (1968:July)
- Collective Bargaining Today, 1969; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining Today, 1969; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Author: David L. Cole; Theodore W. Kheel; Albert Shanker; Saul Wallen; A. H. Raskin; Howard D. Samuel; Douglas Soutar
    Notes: Authors include: Joseph P. Molony; Edmund J. Flynn; Solomon Barkin; Matthew A. Kelly; John R. Cooke; Joseph A. Beirne; Owen Fairweather; Theodore W. Kheel; David L. Cole; Joseph R. Crowley; Thomas R. Donahue; Albert Shanker; Jerry Wurf; Saul Wallen; A. H. Raskin; Gordon H. Cole; Howard D. Samuel; Kenneth B. Clark; George G. Higgins; Paul W. McCracken; Nathaniel Goldfinger; Frank L. Fernbach; I. W. Abel; Everett M. Goulard; George W. Taylor; Joseph S. Murphy; J. Curtis Counts; Vernon E. Jirikowic; Herbert Bienstock; Paul Jennings; Sam Kagel; Harry J. Link; Frank W. McCulloch; Douglas Soutar; Thomas E. Harris; Arnold Ordman; Kenneth C. McGuiness; Elliot Bredhoff; Thompson Powers; Louis Sherman
  - Item 2: Collective Bargaining Today, 1969; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: Authors include: Joseph P. Molony; Edmund J. Flynn; Solomon Barkin; Matthew A. Kelly; John R. Cooke; Joseph A. Beirne; Owen Fairweather; Theodore W. Kheel; David L. Cole; Joseph R. Crowley; Thomas R. Donahue; Albert Shanker; Jerry Wurf; Saul Wallen; A. H. Raskin; Gordon H. Cole; Howard D. Samuel; Kenneth B. Clark; George G. Higgins; Paul W. McCracken; Nathaniel Goldfinger; Frank L. Fernbach; I. W. Abel; Everett M. Goulard; George W. Taylor; Joseph S. Murphy; J. Curtis Counts; Vernon E. Jirikowic; Herbert Bienstock; Paul Jennings; Sam Kagel; Harry J. Link; Frank W. McCulloch; Douglas Soutar; Thomas E. Harris; Arnold Ordman; Kenneth C. McGuiness; Elliot Bredhoff; Thompson Powers; Louis Sherman. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Collective Bargaining Today, 1969; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Notes: Authors include: Joseph P. Molony; Edmund J. Flynn; Solomon Barkin; Matthew A. Kelly; John R. Cooke; Joseph A. Beirne; Owen Fairweather; Theodore W. Kheel; David L. Cole; Joseph R. Crowley; Thomas R. Donahue; Albert Shanker; Jerry Wurf; Saul Wallen; A. H. Raskin; Gordon H. Cole; Howard D. Samuel; Kenneth B. Clark; George G. Higgins; Paul W. McCracken; Nathaniel Goldfinger; Frank L. Fernbach; I. W. Abel; Everett M. Goulard; George W. Taylor; Joseph S. Murphy; J. Curtis Counts; Vernon E. Jirikowic; Herbert Bienstock; Paul Jennings; Sam Kagel; Harry J. Link; Frank W. McCulloch; Douglas Soutar; Thomas E. Harris; Arnold Ordman; Kenneth C. McGuiness; Elliot Bredhoff; Thompson Powers; Louis Sherman. Copy 3.
- Collective Bargaining Today, 1971; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining Today, 1971; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Author: George Meany; Theodore W. Kheel; Evelyn Dubrow
    Notes: Authors include: Theodore W. Kheel; George P. Shultz; Lloyd Ulman; Joseph A. Beirne; George W. Taylor; Nathaniel Goldfinger; George P. Hitchings; J. D. Hodgson; George Meany; Charles C. Killingsworth; James E. Wolfe; William W. Winpisinger; Robert Carr; Benjamin C. Roberts; Eugene D. Glover; Benjamin Aaron; Irving Abramson; Malcom Denise; Martin E. Segal; Dan M. McGill; Leonard Woodcock; Richard M. Scammon; Malcolm R. Lovell; Milton A. Galamison; Evelyn Dubrow; Velma M. Hill; Patrick Owens; William J. Eaton; Eugene Roberts; Harry Bernstein; Edward T. Townsend; Damon Stetson; James P. Gannon; Victor Feather
  - Item 2: Collective Bargaining Today, 1971; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: Authors include: Theodore W. Kheel; George P. Shultz; Lloyd Ulman; Joseph A. Beirne; George W. Taylor; Nathaniel Goldfinger; George P. Hitchings; J. D. Hodgson; George Meany; Charles C. Killingsworth; James E. Wolfe; William W. Winpisinger; Robert Carr; Benjamin C. Roberts; Eugene D. Glover; Benjamin Aaron; Irving Abramson; Malcom Denise; Martin E. Segal; Dan M. McGill; Leonard Woodcock; Richard M. Scammon; Malcolm R. Lovell; Milton A. Galamison; Evelyn Dubrow; Velma M. Hill; Patrick Owens; William J. Eaton; Eugene Roberts; Harry Bernstein; Edward T. Townsend; Damon Stetson; James P. Gannon; Victor Feather. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Collective Bargaining Today, 1971; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Notes: Authors include: Theodore W. Kheel; George P. Shultz; Lloyd Ulman; Joseph A. Beirne; George W. Taylor; Nathaniel Goldfinger; George P. Hitchings; J. D. Hodgson; George Meany; Charles C. Killingsworth; James E. Wolfe; William W. Winpisinger; Robert Carr; Benjamin C. Roberts; Eugene D. Glover; Benjamin Aaron; Irving Abramson; Malcom Denise; Martin E. Segal; Dan M. McGill; Leonard Woodcock; Richard M. Scammon; Malcolm R. Lovell; Milton A. Galamison; Evelyn Dubrow; Velma M. Hill; Patrick Owens; William J. Eaton; Eugene Roberts; Harry Bernstein; Edward T. Townsend; Damon Stetson; James P. Gannon; Victor Feather. Copy 3.
- Colonial Santo Domingo: Its Leading Monuments, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Colonial Santo Domingo: Its Leading Monuments, 1998; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Author: EDUCA
- The Convention Center: Building First, Planning Later, 1973; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Convention Center: Building First, Planning Later, 1973; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Notes: Published in The Village Voice, v.18:no.17 (1973:Apr. 26)
- Cornell Law Review, 1972; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Cornell Law Review, 1972; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Author: Arnold S. Jacobs
    Notes: v.57:no.6 (1972:July)
  - Item 2: Cornell Law Review, 1972; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.57:no.6 (1972:July). Copy 2.
- Cornell Law Review, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Cornell Law Review, 1999; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Author: Carl S. Bjerre; Jeanne L. Schroeder; Joseph S. Klapach; Daniel E. Wenner
    Notes: v.84:no.2 (1999:Jan.)
- Cornell Law Review, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Cornell Law Review, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Author: Stephen P. Garvey; Sheri Lynn Johnson; Paul Marcus; Robert A. Schapiro; Robert A. Hillman; Jeffrey J. Rachlinski; Gregory S. Alexander; David C. Mayer; Alison J. Nathan
    Notes: v.85:no.3 (2000:Mar.)
  - Item 2: Cornell Law Review, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Author: Yale Kamisar; Steven L. Schwarcz; Stewart E. Sterk; Chad King
    Notes: v.85:no.4 (2000:May)
  - Item 3: Cornell Law Review, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Author: Angela P. Harris; Tracy E. Higgins; Laura A. Rosenbury; Linda C. McClain; Devon W. Carbado; Mitu Gulati; Martha R. Mahoney; Darren Lenard Hutchinson; Julie A. Nice; Kathryn Abrams; Mary Anne Case; Marissa J. Holob
    Notes: v.85:no.5 (2000:July)
  - Item 4: Cornell Law Review, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Author: Frank B. Cross; Kent Greenawalt; Jung S. Hahm; Stacey A. Miness; Nicholas R. Spampata
    Notes: v.85:no.6 (2000:Sep.)
- Cornell Law Review, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Cornell Law Review, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Author: Frank B. Cross; Stephen J. Ceci; Richard D. Friedman; Julie Goldscheid; Jason A. Jones; Adam J. Siegel; James E. Fleming
    Notes: v.86:no.1 (2000:Nov.)
  - Item 2: Cornell Law Review, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Author: Robin Fretwell Wilson; Christopher Bryant; Timothy J. Simeone; John H. Blume; Stephen P. Garvey; Sheri Lynn Johnson; Oren Eisner; David T. Huang
    Notes: v.86:no.2 (2001:Jan.)
  - Item 3: Cornell Law Review, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Author: Lynn S. Branham; Ann Juliano; Stewart J. Schwab; Samuel M. Bayard; Erin E. Buzuvis; Steven K. Green; Steven H. Shiffrin
    Notes: v.86:no.3 (2001:Mar.)
  - Item 4: Cornell Law Review, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Author: Sheryll D. Cashin; Chris Guthrie; Jeffrey J. Rachlinski; William K. Kelly; Christopher Y. Chen; Randal I. Goldstein
    Notes: v.86:no.4 (2001:May)
  - Item 5: Cornell Law Review, 2001; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Author: Chirs William Sanchirico; Gary J. Simson; Stephen P. Garvey; Forrest G. Alogna
    Notes: v.86:no.5 (2001:July)
- Cornell Law Review, 2004; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Cornell Law Review, 2004; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Author: John C. Coffee, Jr.; John S. Baker, Jr.; Arnoud W. A. Boot; Jonathan R. Macey; Geoffrey P. Miller; Hillary A. Sale; Charles M. Elson; Yaniv Grinstein; Karl A. Groskaufmanis; John F. Olson; Barry W. Rashkover
    Notes: v.89:no.2 (2004:Jan.)
- Cornell's Research Serves the Region, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Cornell's Research Serves the Region: Small Business Development, 2002; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Author: Office of the Vice Provost for Research
- "Dear Herm" with a Cast of Dozens, 1974; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: "Dear Herm" with a Cast of Dozens, 1974; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: Leo rosten
    Notes: Signed by author
- The Definition of a Fiduciary Under ERISA: Basic Principles, 1992; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Definition of a Fiduciary Under ERISA: Basic Principles, 1992; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Author: Jane Kheel Stanley
    Notes: Published in Real Property Probate and Trust Journal, v.27:no.2 (1992:Summer)
- Development and the Environment, 1992; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Development and the Environment, 1992; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Author: International Bank for Reconstruction and Development; The World Bank
    Notes: World Development Report, 1992: World Development Indicators
- Done Deals, 2000; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Done Deals: Venture Capitalists Tell Their Stories, 2000; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Author: Udayan Gupta
- The Dumbest Moments in Business History, 2004; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Dumbest Moments in Business History: Useless Products, Ruinous Deals, Clueless Bosses and Other Signs of Unintellegent Life in the Workplace, 2004; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Author: Adam Horowitz; Mark Athitakis; Mark Lasswell
- Eduational Theatre Management, 1972; Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Educational Theatre Management, 1972; Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Author: John E. Clifford
- Edward Via Virginia College of Osteopathic Medicine, 2002; Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Edward Via Virginia College of Osteopathic Medicine, 2002; Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Author: Edward Via Virginia College of Osteopathic Medicine
    Notes: Student information packet
  - Item 2: Edward Via Virginia College of Osteopathic Medicine, 2002; Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Notes: Student information packet. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Edward Via Virginia College of Osteopathic Medicine, 2002; Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Notes: Student information packet. Copy 3.
- An Essay on Bargaining, 1960; Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: An Essay on Bargaining, 1960; Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Author: Thomas C. Schelling
    Notes: Chapter 2 from The Strategy of Conflict
- The Ethical Basis of Economic Freedom, 1976; Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Ethical Basis of Economic Freedom, 1976; Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Author: Ivan Hill
    Notes: Authors include: Ivan Hill; James L. Peacock; Roy A. Rappaport; J. B. Condliffe; Wolfram Fischer; Jack N. Behrman; Max H. Parrott; Leon Jaworski; C. E. Grease; Andrew W. Kneier; Kenneth Fiester; Arch N. Booth; Neil H. Offen; Rea W. Smith; Stockton Helffrich; Mark Ethridge, Jr.; H. Jackson Pontius; William D. Murray; Glen D. King; Earl W. Kintner; William E. Simon
- An Exercise in Human Relations, 1957; Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: An Exercise in Human Relations, 1957; Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Author: Institute of Economic Affairs; Theodore W. Kheel
    Notes: Interview of Theodore Kheel published in Challenge, v.5:no.9/10 (1957:June/July)
- Exorcising the Ghost at La Pavilion, 1970; Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Exorcising the Ghost at La Pavillon, 1970; Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Author: Gael Greene
    Notes: Published in New York, v.3:no.38 (1970:Sep. 21)
  - Item 2: Exorcising the Ghost at La Pavillon, 1970; Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Notes: Published in New York, v.3:no.38 (1970:Sep. 21). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Chere amie:, 1970; Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Notes: September 21, 1970. Letter from Theodore Kheel to Gael Greene regarding article in New York magazine about La Pavilion. On letterhead.
  - Item 4: Chere amie:, 1970; Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Notes: September 21, 1970. Letter from Theodore Kheel to Gael Greene regarding article in New York magazine about La Pavilion. On letterhead. Copy 2.
  - Item 5: Chere amie:, 1970; Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Notes: September 21, 1970. Letter from Theodore Kheel to Gael Greene regarding article in New York magazine about La Pavilion. On letterhead. Copy 3.
  - Item 6: Dear Gael:, 1970; Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Notes: September 21, 1970. Letter from Theodore Kheel to Gael Greene regarding article in New York magazine about La Pavilion. Draft.
- Exploring Alternatives to the Strike, 1973; Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Exploring Alternatives to the Strike, 1973; Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Notes: Reprint from Monthly Labor Review, September, 1973.
- Fact Sheet: Section 6606, 1971; Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Fact Sheet: Section 6606, 1971; Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Notes: Press conference, March 4, 1971.
  - Item 2: Fact Sheet: Section 6606, 1971; Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Notes: Press conference, March 4, 1971. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Fact Sheet: Section 6606, 1971; Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Notes: Press conference, March 4, 1971. Copy 3.
  - Item 4: Fact Sheet: Section 6606, 1971; Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Notes: Statement before a joint hearing of the Committee on Corporations, Authorites and Commission of the New York State Assembly and the Autonomous Study Commission of the Legislature of New Jersey, March 5, 1971.
  - Item 5: Fact Sheet: Section 6606, 1971; Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Notes: Statement before a joint hearing of the Committee on Corporations, Authorites and Commission of the New York State Assembly and the Autonomous Study Commission of the Legislature of New Jersey, March 5, 1971. Copy 2.
  - Item 6: Fact Sheet: Section 6606, 1971; Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Notes: Statement before a joint hearing of the Committee on Corporations, Authorites and Commission of the New York State Assembly and the Autonomous Study Commission of the Legislature of New Jersey, March 5, 1971. Copy 3.
- Fear's Empire, 2003; Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Fear's Empire: War, Terrorism, and Democracy, 2003; Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Author: Benjamin R. Barber
- A Field Guide to North Atlantic Wildlife, 2005; Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: A Field Guide to North Atlantic Wildlife, 2005; Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Author: Noble S. Proctor; Patrick J. Lynch
- The Fight for a Transportation System that Works, 1972; Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Fight for a Transportation System that Works, 1972; Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Notes: Reprint from Lithopinion 26 (1972)
- First Day Issue Cover: Collective Bargaining Stamp, 1975; Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: First Day Issue Cover: Collective Bargaining Stamp, 1975; Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Author: United States Postal Service
  - Item 2: First Day Issue Cover: Collective Bargaining Stamp, 1975; Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: First Day Issue Cover: Collective Bargaining Stamp, 1975; Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Footprints in the Jungle, 2001; Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Footprints in the Jungle, 2001; Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
    Author: Ian A. Bowles; Glenn T. Prickett
- Foreign Affairs, 1978; Publication (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Foreign Affairs: America and the World 1978, Publication (Box 4, Folder 19)
    Author: Hedley Bull; Stanley Hoffman; McGeorge Bundy; Arthur Schlesinger, Jr.; Marina v.N. Whitman; Adam Ulam; David Watt; Stanley Karnow; John C. Campbell; Colin Legum; Richard R. Fagen; Daniel Yankelovich; Elaine P. Adam
    Notes: v.57:no.3 (1979)
- Frank Lloyd Wright, 2004; Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Frank Lloyd Wright, 2004; Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Author: Ada Louise Huxtable
- A Free Ghana Is Born, Inspired By America, 1957; Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: A Free Ghana Is Born, Inspired By America, 1957; Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
    Notes: From the New York Herald Tribune, March 6, 1957.
- From Hiroshima to Future Generations, 1992; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: From Hiroshima to Future Generations: Voices from the Future Generations Alliance Foundation, 1992; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Author: Wendell Bell; Theodore W. Kheel; Kido Inoue; Kim Tae-Chang; Katsuhiko Yazaki
    Language: English and Japanese.
  - Item 2: From Hiroshima to Future Generations: Voices from the Future Generations Alliance Foundation, 1992; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Why Future Generations Now?, 1992; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Author: Wendell Bell; Sakae Shimizu; Kim Tae-Chang; Katsuhiko Yazaki; Emmanuel Agius; Allen Tough; Rick A. Slaughter
- Giving In America, 1975; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Giving In America: Toward a Stronger Voluntary Sector, 1975; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Author: Commission on Private Philanthropy and Public Need
- Global Dumping Ground, 1990; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Global Dumping Ground: The International Traffic in Hazardous Waste, 1990; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Author: Center for Investigative Reporting; Bill Moyers
- Gold Coast Becomes Democracy this Week, 1957; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Gold Coast Becomes Democracy this Week: Adopts Ancient Name of Ghana; Nixon to Attend Wednesday Fete, 1957; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Notes: From the New York Herald Tribune, March 3, 1957.
  - Item 2: Gold Coast Becomes Democracy this Week: Adopts Ancient Name of Ghana; Nixon to Attend Wednesday Fete, 1957; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Notes: From the New York Herald Tribune, March 3, 1957. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Gold Coast Becomes Democracy this Week: Adopts Ancient Name of Ghana; Nixon to Attend Wednesday Fete, 1957; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Notes: From the New York Herald Tribune, March 3, 1957. Copy 3.
- The Golden Age of Jazz, 1979; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Golden Age of Jazz, 1979; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Author: William P. Gottlieb
- Guide to Gifts and Bequests: 1980-1982, Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Guide to Gifts and Bequests: 1980-1982, Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Author: Institutions Press
    Notes: A Directory of Philanthropically Supported Institutions: New York, New Jersey, Pennsylvania
- Guidelines, Informal Controls, and the Market Place, 1966; Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Guidelines, Informal Controls, and the Market Place, 1966; Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Author: George P. Shultz; Robert Z. Aliber